[{"question": "How many women and men are in New Zealand's cabinet after the promotion of Willow-Jean Prime?", "answer": "10 women and 10 men"}, {"question": "What year was The Satanic Verses released, according to the excerpt?", "answer": "1988"}, {"question": "What percentage did Pat Cullen mention was a red line during the protests?", "answer": "10%"}, {"question": "According to Prof Bryan Williams, how many deaths globally are caused by high blood pressure each year?", "answer": "10 million"}, {"question": "What percentage pay rise are junior doctors demanding, according to Dr. Vivek Trivedi?", "answer": "35%"}, {"question": "What is the half-life of one of the plutonium isotopes mentioned in the Crawford Lake sediments?", "answer": "24,000 years"}, {"question": "According to Dr Vanessa Saliba from the UK Health Security Agency, how long must there be no detections of poliovirus in London before the UK can be declared no longer an infected country?", "answer": "12 months"}, {"question": "Which newly passed act allowed Ms. Carroll to bring the civil case against Mr. Trump?", "answer": "Adult Survivors Act"}, {"question": "At what event was the film 'The Deepest Breath' screened in January?", "answer": "Sundance Film Festival"}, {"question": "Who led the independent review that called for a 'fundamentally different' model of care for children with gender dysphoria?", "answer": "Dr Hilary Cass"}, {"question": "What symptom of sepsis does not fade when a glass is rolled over it?", "answer": "a rash that does not fade when a glass is rolled over it"}, {"question": "What are the Meiteis' views on buying land or settling in the hill districts?", "answer": "they and other non-tribal people are not allowed to buy land or settle in the hill districts"}, {"question": "What was the total cost of the damage and consequential costs caused by the pro-Palestinian protesters at Teledyne Labtech?", "answer": "\u00a31.2m"}, {"question": "What wording did Evolv change its homepage text to after initially changing it from 'Weapons-Free Zones'?", "answer": "Safe Zones"}, {"question": "Who did James Corden replace when he took over The Late Late Show in 2015?", "answer": "Craig Ferguson"}, {"question": "How deep is the Titanic wreck?", "answer": "3,810m (12,500ft)"}, {"question": "What club was Graham Potter managing when he suffered a 4-1 defeat at his former club Brighton?", "answer": "Chelsea"}, {"question": "What did Paris Mayo use to suffocate her infant son Stanley?", "answer": "cotton wool"}, {"question": "What year did Andy Murray last win a title on clay before his 2023 victory in Aix-en-Provence?", "answer": "2016"}, {"question": "How many WhatsApp messages linked to Matt Hancock's time as health secretary were obtained by the Telegraph?", "answer": "more than 100,000"}, {"question": "How much did teacher salaries fall by between 2010 and 2022, according to the Institute for Fiscal Studies?", "answer": "11%"}, {"question": "How many hours of police time did Humberside Police reportedly save per month by testing the policy?", "answer": "1,441 hours"}, {"question": "At what age did Jiang Yanyong pass away?", "answer": "aged 91"}, {"question": "When will the King be crowned alongside Camilla, the Queen Consort?", "answer": "on 6 May"}, {"question": "On what date did Tucker Carlson host his last TV programme on Fox News?", "answer": "Friday 21 April"}, {"question": "What is the starting salary for teachers in England expected to rise to by September?", "answer": "\u00a330,000 a year"}, {"question": "When was Ryan Mason previously in charge of Tottenham?", "answer": "2021"}, {"question": "What time does Saturday's Coronation begin?", "answer": "11:00 BST"}, {"question": "What specific month is designated as Mental Health Awareness Month in the US, according to the excerpt?", "answer": "May"}, {"question": "What is the half-life of the plutonium isotope being looked at by the University of Southampton scientists?", "answer": "24,000 years"}, {"question": "What was the name of the police investigation into the SNP's finances?", "answer": "Operation Branchform"}, {"question": "What legal act allowed Ms Carroll to bring a civil case against Mr Trump?", "answer": "the Adult Survivors Act"}, {"question": "How long did Paris Mayo's jury deliberate before convicting her of murder?", "answer": "eight hours and 38 minutes"}, {"question": "Who was the head of OceanGate that died on 18 June?", "answer": "Stockton Rush"}, {"question": "At what time were residents asked to leave by police according to Susan?", "answer": "about 07:00 BST"}, {"question": "Who was in imperious form as he came from sixth on the grid to win the Belgian Grand Prix?", "answer": "Max Verstappen"}, {"question": "At what time did the break-in happen at Twiglet's owner's house?", "answer": "about 15:00 BST"}, {"question": "Where will banks in the UK be able to borrow money from instead of the open market?", "answer": "the Bank of England"}, {"question": "According to Ms Cullen, what was the status of all the exemptions requested by Great Ormond Street Hospital?", "answer": "All of the exemptions that Great Ormond Street requested of the Royal College of Nursing were granted earlier yesterday."}, {"question": "How many parties initially faced charges in December 2020 related to the White Island eruption?", "answer": "Thirteen parties"}, {"question": "What did the Wimbledon crowd do after Venus Williams' 24th Open era appearance ended?", "answer": "received a standing ovation"}, {"question": "What is the length marine reptiles mentioned in the excerpt could grow up to?", "answer": "12m-long"}, {"question": "How many days did Imogen spend in NICU at Swansea before being moved to the Princess of Wales Hospital?", "answer": "98 days"}, {"question": "From which age would people be able to apply for a gender recognition certificate (GRC) under the proposed Gender Recognition Bill in Scotland?", "answer": "16"}, {"question": "When is the new government public warning system test expected to take place?", "answer": "23 April"}, {"question": "Which water company's chief financial officer also decided to decline his bonus?", "answer": "Thames Water"}, {"question": "How many days passed since Putin shattered European security before Mr Healey criticized the delayed plan?", "answer": "510 days"}, {"question": "How many days did Cathie and Tricia spend travelling from west to east Canada?", "answer": "51 days"}, {"question": "How long was Edward Weeks jailed for after admitting rape?", "answer": "eight years"}, {"question": "How many MiG-29s did Slovakia approve to send to Ukraine, according to the Prime Minister's tweet?", "answer": "13 MiG-29s"}, {"question": "What is Luke's predicted score for the Tottenham match?", "answer": "3-1"}, {"question": "How many days was another 13-year-old Queensland boy with developmental disabilities confined to a cell for 20 hours per day?", "answer": "78 days"}, {"question": "For how many days did Cathie and Tricia travel from west to east Canada?", "answer": "51 days"}, {"question": "Who is the general secretary of the RMT that called the vote a 'de-facto referendum on the dispute'?", "answer": "Mick Lynch"}, {"question": "How many days had students trapped in the headquarters of an oil company in Khartoum gone without food or water?", "answer": "three days"}, {"question": "How many pupils referred to the EWS by schools were on a waiting list at the end of March 2023?", "answer": "1,751"}, {"question": "Who were the rulers that attended a garden party at Hillsborough Castle, marking their first official visit outside England since the coronation?", "answer": "King Charles and Queen Camilla"}, {"question": "At what local time was the bright glow observed in the sky over Kyiv?", "answer": "around 22:00 local time"}, {"question": "What is the distance from Earth to the event called AT2021lwx as calculated by Dr. Philip Wiseman's team?", "answer": "8bn light years away"}, {"question": "How many people were treated at the scene of the incident at Imperial Dock in Leith?", "answer": "12 people"}, {"question": "How many inquiries and inquests have been conducted regarding the case of Mr. Morgan's death?", "answer": "five inquiries and an inquest"}, {"question": "How many birds does Ioan Humphreys have on his farm?", "answer": "32,000 birds"}, {"question": "In which year did Fiona Wightman split from comedian Paul Whitehouse while also facing a cancer diagnosis?", "answer": "2000"}, {"question": "What date did all five people on board the Titan submersible die?", "answer": "18 June"}, {"question": "How many pages did the thirty-seven documents found in the locked cabinet at New Scotland Yard span?", "answer": "95 pages"}, {"question": "How much did commuter Mimi Kihumulendi say it costs to commute from Reading to London for a year?", "answer": "nearly \u00a36,000"}, {"question": "What is the highest level the Fed's key interest rate has reached since 2007, according to the excerpt?", "answer": "4.75%-5%"}, {"question": "What is the length of time for which the Treherbert line will close as part of the Valleys network electrification?", "answer": "around ten months"}, {"question": "What type of courtroom has been set up inside the prison for Navalny's trial?", "answer": "temporary courtroom"}, {"question": "How many years ago did David and Janice Hunter retire to Cyprus?", "answer": "20 years ago"}, {"question": "At what time did the incident with the Petrel begin, according to Dales Marine Services?", "answer": "08:00"}, {"question": "What did Alex Murdaugh pocket from the Satterfield's insurance policies?", "answer": "$4.3m"}, {"question": "What is the estimated number of Twitter Blue subscribers in March 2023 according to Sensor Tower?", "answer": "around 386,000"}, {"question": "Which royal family member shook hands with Dean of Windsor David Conner as she left the chapel?", "answer": "Princess Charlotte"}, {"question": "How many YouTube views did Bad Bunny's track Dos Mil 16 acquire after the release of Un Verano Sin Ti?", "answer": "60 million"}, {"question": "How many tourists did Ibiza receive last year?", "answer": "four million"}, {"question": "What color tablets are thought to be benzodiazepines according to the Public Health Agency?", "answer": "yellow tablets"}, {"question": "According to the text, who has the right to disclose military plans publicly in Ukraine?", "answer": "the president, the minister of defence, and the commander in chief"}, {"question": "What are the names of the two species that have been added to the newly named Saurona genus?", "answer": "Saurona triangular and Saurona aurigera"}, {"question": "Which two cities in the UK will see job creation related to the construction of the new submarine model SSN-AUKUS?", "answer": "Derby and Barrow-in-Furness"}, {"question": "Which song did Elton John dedicate to George Michael during his final show in the UK at Glastonbury?", "answer": "Don't Let The Sun Go Down On Me"}, {"question": "What did the IDF and ISA say is their mission regarding abductees?", "answer": "to locate and return the abductees home"}, {"question": "What did Chief Constable Pam Kelly say about the content shared with Gwent Police?", "answer": "The content shared with us is vile"}, {"question": "At what age did Wendy Reilly make her debut for Wales?", "answer": "16"}, {"question": "What specific ailment does a grey squirrel transmit that is lethal to red squirrels?", "answer": "squirrelpox virus"}, {"question": "What phrase did Vladimir Putin use to clarify the funding status of Wagner after the mutiny?", "answer": "100% funded by the Russian state"}, {"question": "How many episodes of The Wire were aired between 2002 and 2008?", "answer": "60 episodes"}, {"question": "How many signatures has the petition gathered so far calling for a review of the inspection at Caversham Primary?", "answer": "more than 150,000"}, {"question": "What was Luke's prediction for the score between Spurs and their opponent?", "answer": "3-1"}, {"question": "How many fake reviews did Amazon block last year as a result of their new methods?", "answer": "over 200 million"}, {"question": "What was the hush money payment to porn star Stormy Daniels related to, according to the excerpt?", "answer": "to hide damaging information ahead of the 2016 election"}, {"question": "How many specialist lighting fixtures have been fitted at the Eurovision venue?", "answer": "more than 2,000"}, {"question": "What is the specific time that the full BBC interview with Schofield will be available on iPlayer?", "answer": "from 06:00 BST on Friday"}, {"question": "What was the mandatory minimum sentence for Cartagena's crime according to the court papers?", "answer": "five years in prison"}, {"question": "Which major Russian outlets were silenced, shut down, or blocked after the war began?", "answer": "TV Rain, Echo of Moscow radio and newspaper Novaya Gazeta"}, {"question": "According to the report, what did the police wrongly tell Ernest Moret he would not be able to do if convicted for not sharing his PINs?", "answer": "never be able to travel internationally again"}, {"question": "What excuse did Bevan provide for Lola's injuries during the trial?", "answer": "a fall down the stairs, after the family's dog pushed her"}, {"question": "Who are the owners of the car company Stellantis?", "answer": "Vauxhall, Peugeot, Citroen and Fiat"}, {"question": "What was Harman's only missed putt from inside 10 feet for the week?", "answer": "on the short 13th"}, {"question": "What are the weight-related health conditions listed by NICE that could make someone with a lower obese BMI range eligible for semaglutide?", "answer": "pre-diabetic, has type 2 diabetes, high blood pressure, heart disease or obstructive sleep apnoea"}]